<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Salesforce to SAP S/4HANA Order Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
This Anypoint template serves as a foundation for setting an online sync of orders from Salesforce to SAP S/4HANA.
Use this template if would like to sync orders from Salesforce to SAP S/4HANA sales orders in manner of one time synchronization by browse toting the HTTP endpoint. The template will fetch all orders by specified criteria and send it to SAP S/4HANA to create/update sales order. Requirements have been set not only to be used as examples, but also to establish a starting point to adapt your integration to your requirements.
As implemented, this template leverages the Mule batch module. The batch job is divided into Process and On Complete stages. 
The integration is triggered by the HTTP endpoint to fetch all the Salesforce Orders suitable for migration. Fetched orders are passed to the batch as input. In the batch the sales order is fetched from SAP S/4HANA by its order number. If it exists, its sales order identifier is resolved against SAP S/4HANA. If it doesn't exist, then new sales order is fetched from SAP S/4HANA. Afterwards every sales order from Salesforce is sent to SAP S/4HANA where it is asynchronously updated or created. Finally during the On Complete stage the template logs output statistics data into the console and sends a notification e-mail with the results of the batch execution.</section>
		<section id="considerations">
​To make this template run, there are certain preconditions that must be considered. All of them deal with the preparations in both source (Salesforce) and destination (SAP S4Hana) systems, that must be made for the template to run smoothly.
**Failing to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**

Before using this template, you may want to check out this [Documentation Page](https://docs.mulesoft.com/connectors/sap/sap-s4hana-cloud-connector), that will teach you how to work
with SAP S/4HANA and Anypoint Studio.
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_studio">
After you import your template into Anypoint Studio, follow these steps to run it:

+ Locate the properties file `mule.dev.properties`, in src/main/resources.
+ Complete all the properties required as per the examples in the "Properties to Configure" section.
+ Right click the template project folder.
+ Hover your mouse over `Run as`.
+ Click `Mule Application (configure)`.
+ Inside the dialog, select Environment and set the variable `mule.env` to the value `dev`.
+ Click `Run`.

In order to make this template run on Anypoint Studio there are a few extra steps that needs to be made.
Please check this Documentation Page:

+ [Enabling Your Studio Project for SAP S/4HANA](https://docs.mulesoft.com/connectors/sap/sap-s4hana-cloud-connector)	
		</section>
		<section id="sfdcsrc">
​If the user who configured the template for the source system does not have at least *read only* permissions for the fields that are fetched, then an *InvalidFieldFault* API fault displays.

```
java.lang.RuntimeException: [InvalidFieldFault [ApiQueryFault
[ApiFault  exceptionCode='INVALID_FIELD'
exceptionMessage='Id,  OrderNumber,  EffectiveDate, Status, SAP4HANA_Order_Key__c
^
ERROR at Row:1:Column:486
No such column 'SAP4HANA_Order_Key' on entity 'Order'. If you are attempting to
use a custom field, be sure to append the '__c' after the custom field name.
Reference your WSDL or the describe call for the appropriate names.'
]
row='1'
column='486'
]
]
```
		</section>
		<section id="s4hana_dst">
		
Here's what you need to know about SAP S/4HANA to get this template to work.
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
**Application Configuration**
+ http.port `9090`
+ page.size `1000`

**SoldToParty Configuration: The sold-to party is contractually responsible for sales orders.**
+ s4hana.soldToParty `123456`

**Watermarking default last query timestamp e.g. 2017-12-13T03:00:59Z**
+ watermark.default.expression `2019-07-13T03:00:59Z`

**SalesForce Connector Configuration**

+ sfdc.username `bob.dylan@sfdc`
+ sfdc.password `DylanPassword123`
+ sfdc.securityToken `avsfwCUl7apQs56Xq2AKi3X`

**SAP S/4HANA Connector Configuration**

+ s4hana.baseUrl `your.s4hana.address.com`
+ s4hana.username `your.s4hana.username`
+ s4hana.password `your.s4hana.password`

**SMTP Services Configuration**

+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `email@example.com`
+ smtp.password `password`

**Email Details**

+ mail.from `batch.migrateOrders.migration@mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `your@email.com`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job Finished Report`
​
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
		
There are no particular considerations for this template regarding API calls
		</section>
<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
        <![CDATA[
This is the file where you will found the inbound and outbound sides of your integration app.
This Template has a [HTTP Listener Connector](https://docs.mulesoft.com/connectors/http/http-listener-ref) as the way to trigger the use case.
​
$H$H# Trigger Flow
**HTTP Listener Connector** - Start Report Generation
​
+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migrateorders` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.
​
]]>
        </section>
        
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		<![CDATA[
Functional aspect of the template is implemented on this XML, directed by one flow responsible of executing the logic.
For the purpose of this particular template the *mainFlow* just executes the Batch Job which handles all the logic of it.
This flow has Error Handling that basically consists on invoking the *On Error Propagate Component* defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>